### **DON OMONDI ONYANGO**

Digital Marketer & Graphics Designer

Experience: 3 years | Available: Immediately | Location: Nairobi onyangodonomondi@gmail.com |

+254741590670 || 0748453590

### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a qualified graphic design specialist. Over three years ago, I started working as a graphic designer. I have therefore acquired all the creative skills necessary to produce a visual concept that unquestionably serves as a channel of communication with customers, clients, sponsors, etc.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **K24 TELEVISION**

Graduate Intern | Television production

Nairobi, Kenya

2020-09-01 | 2020-11-01

 Handling Pre-Production, Production and Post Production assignment as guided by the supervisor.

## **DEKILA LIMITED**

Graphic designer Nairobi, Kenya

2021-08-01 | present

- Designing vectors and illustrations for branding purposes.
- Digital marketing across social media platforms.
- maintaining online social media presence and updating the company website.

# **ZION PEARL PUBLISHER**

Graphics designer | Nairobi Kenya

Nairobi, Kenya

2021-08-01 | 2021-012-01

- Designing book covers.
- Making Poster flyers and weekly print Magazines.

## **EDUCATION:**

## MOI UNIVERSITY

• Bachelors' Degree in Film & Media Studies

# ORIWO BOYS HIGH SCHOOL

• KCSE CERTFICATE B 63 POINTS

# **OBER BOYS' PRIMARY**

• KCPE CERTFICATE 370 MARKS

### **SKILLS**

- Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Acrobat, Premier Pro & After Effects.
- Print knowledge/designing for print
- Marketing and branding
- Logo creation
- Social media

## **PORTFOLIO**

• https://onyangodonomondi.github.io/portfoliog

### **REFEREES**

## Mr. Bii Cosmas

Lecturer Moi University,

Tel: 0721485349

## Mr. Derick Kithela

CEO DEKILA LTD,

Tel: 0712095724